Shiya.
Sorry.
I'm late.
That's okay.
All these years,
I've owed you a proper date.
We
really haven't had a meal alone together.
It's always either Jingyan or Peining.
Hurry up, Peining.
Over here.
The traffic was terrible.
Hope you didn't wait too long.
Waiter.
Two more sets of tableware, please.
Why are you guys so late?
It's all Pei Ning's fault.
I said we should ride the motorcycle,
but he insisted on driving.
I was afraid Shiya would drink too much,
and the wind would give her a headache on the motorcycle.
I am the one taking Shiya home.
Brother,
from now on,
let me do it.
Neither of you should fight over it.
Shiya is mine.
Today's theme
is
to celebrate Pei Song
and Shiya being single again.
Come.
Pei Song,
raise your glass.
Shiya.
I thought today
was just the two of us.
We're already divorced.
It's not appropriate to eat alone.
Do you really have to push things
this far?
I don't know what you mean.
Do you really not understand,
or are you just pretending?
Sorry.
I really don't understand.
Cheers.
Come on.
What are you doing, Pei Song?
Are you crazy?
Song Shiya.
I can divorce you.
And I respect your choice.
After the divorce,
you can be with whoever you want.
But as for Pei Ning,
I will not allow it.
That's a bit unreasonable.
Why?
I can't.
Our Pei family is, after all,
a prestigious enterprise.
Every move we make
is under the scrutiny of the media.
If you get together with Song Shiya,
what will the public say?
The Pei family's younger brother-in-law and sister-in-law are together.
People who don't know the truth
will embellish the story.
Do you know that?
I don't mind.
You might not mind,
but what about the whole Pei family?
And what about Shiya?
Are you going to let her, a woman,
bear all this gossip?
I don't mind either.
Shiya,
don't...
Brother.
Since I was a child,
whatever you said,
I would do it.
But not this time.
No.
Let's go.
Shiya.
Pei Ning.
How did a nice meal end up like this?
Pei Song, you went a bit too far just now.
You're staying to eat with me, right?
Psycho.
Sorry about just now.
I lost control a bit.
It's fine.
Well,
regarding my brother,
do you really have no feelings for him?
We are in a contract marriage.
A contract marriage?
When I was in college,
my brother got into gambling debt.
I had to drop out and work to pay it off.
Later, I went on a blind date
and unexpectedly met Pei Song.
His grandfather was pressing him hard,
so he came up with this idea.
By the way.
I...
Tomorrow,
my newly developed smart home system
is going online.
I want to hold a live-stream launch.
Shiya.
Can you
join me?
Sure.
Where is it?
I'll send it to you later.
Family and friends watching the live stream,
hello.
I am Pei Ning.
I'm glad you are all
tuning in for my smart system.
Actually, over the years,
there has been someone
silently encouraging me.
Without her,
this development wouldn't exist.
She is like a star
that lights up my entire night sky.
Without her,
I wouldn't have dared to dream big,
nor would I have thought
of exploring the smart home sector.
Shiya.
I love you.
Marry me.
Song Shiya,
marry me.
That's your sister-in-law.
Pei Song.
You're already divorced.
Pei Song,
do you know
why I divorced you?
Because you're arrogant
and always act so superior.
I'll say it again.
We are already divorced.
It looks like
Pei Ning has already taken the bait.
So,
you are going to put on a show
to provoke Pei Ning
and force him to propose to you?
The sooner I get together with him,
the sooner I can find the evidence
and save more people from becoming victims.
Then what are you going to do?
Does it still hurt?
I'm fine.
But to be honest,
you went a bit too far that day.
Given your personality,
you wouldn't act like that.
If it were in the past,
I probably wouldn't have.
But now I...
What are you smiling at?
I'm smiling because you also have moments of helplessness.
It feels like no matter what you encounter,
you remain calm
and steady.
It's as if anything
can be solved by you.
At a time like this,
you can still smile.
Is there really no other way?
Are you jealous?
What do you think?
Shiya,
when we got married,
we didn't take wedding photos.
Let's go take some tomorrow.